(Sheldon(entering):)Go away?
(Leonard(in a Yoda voice):)Hmm.
(Sheldon(entering):)Could it be me?
(Penny(opening door):)Hey, guys, what's up?
We need a hot 15-year-old Asian girl
with a thing for smart guys.
(Leonard:)- What?
- Howard, that's racist.
Any 15-year-old girl will do the trick.
(Raj:)It's possible
she may have misunderstood us.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- Dr. Cooper. Oh, are we interrupting?
- No, no, please come in.
(Sheldon:)I think you'll appreciate this.
This is very exciting.
(Gablehouser:)- What are you working on?
- Something remarkable.
(Sheldon:)Since my prospects for the Nobel Prize
in Physics have disappeared... Thank you.
(Sheldon:)...I've decided to refocus my efforts
and use my people skills...
(Sheldon:)...to win the Nobel Peace Prize.
(Sheldon:)Look, I'm going
to solve the Middle East crisis...